Remember that time when we met 16 years ago?
You were screwing with my operation even then.
I guess we're cursed by fate.
The strategy and courage you've shown so far is almost admirable.
Still, it seems a little reckless.
Was Babylon's defeat really feasible when you think about it?
Whatever Babylon does now
Doesn't concern me anymore.
I thought at least while I was alive,
If not for the sake of Jian's safety,
Babylon and I could somehow coexist peacefully, and still
You guys just couldn't leave us alone.
You're the ones who attacked us first.
All I did was hit back.
Beating Babylon, winning or losing, none of it interests me.
If winning or losing didn't interest you at all,
Then what made you start murthehelp?
Did you think that Babylon would just sit back and do nothing?
Sit back and do nothing, huh?
You couldn't help yourselves with this bullshit.
You're right.
The first time I saw the murthehelp system,
What most impressed me was its precision.
The way you control the clients and codes
I knew right away that I had to have it.
It's a very good business model.
It was never created for control. Murthehelp wasn't made for that.
Yeah, I get that. I know.
I know you created it to protect your little niece.
That's really touching.
But when you have such a great system, you have to put it to use.
If you aren't doing everything you can to remain competitive,
You'll get left behind.
Jeong Jinman, you're more of an idealist than I thought.
What's so funny?
Because you're not the kind that understands reason.
Hm?
Look at you, you need to control everything.
If it's out of your control, you get scared.
You're the one who's tied down to that chair.
You should be the one that's scared, don't you think?
Doctor, increase the intensity.
Sorry? :cue
Send a video to Jeong Jian, so she knows.
I want her to see the pain she's putting her uncle through.
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
EPISODE 08 LISTEN UP, JINMAN
Fuck!
She made her choice.
We should let her endure it on her own.
Jeong Jinman would want that for her.
We are now connected to murthehelp.
Initiating location tracking of codes.
Excuse me.
Yes?
- Where are you going? - Some of our equipment has seen heavy use.
If we leave it, the server could suffer some damage.
They started out with seven Code Reds in 2012.
And in 2015, they expanded to include Codes Yellow and Purple.
One hundred thirty-four Code Reds active in Korea as of now. :cue
Yellows, 215.
Code Yellows don't move as individuals
But as several corporate-style organizations.
- And that's all? - No, there's more.
Over 700 overseas.
And when you include organizations, Code Purples and Yellows,
Along with client lists and supply chains, the numbers
Well, they start to look massive.
It's far more than we anticipated.
Wait, aren't they already doing business with us?
It seems there's more clients who work with Babylon,
Along with several organizations in Eastern Europe.
So what I'm hearing
Is this entire time they've been nibbling away at Babylon's cash flow,
Stealing our customers.
That while we've been busy,
Jeong Jinman has secretly been waging guerrilla warfare.
I think we should set a meeting with Code Reds
Who aren't loyal to Ahn Seongbeom anymore.
Then we use that information
To discern who we're negotiating with or eliminating.
What criteria should we use?
Hm
Well, for example, we can start by eliminating him.
JW JAEWON CLEANING
Clean up properly.
We lost another one?
Who knows?
They could've gotten killed, or they could have defected.
As of right now, 29 bio chips have been removed. Various codes.
What's worse,
All of our client information was leaked from that server.
Including all our ongoing contracts. We can't reach them.
What if on our side, we delete my uncle's biometric data
And stop Babylon from accessing the server with it?
- Can we do that? - That's impossible.
Murthehelp's original architect is Jeong Jinman.
Jian, it doesn't matter if you're Code Green,
You can't purge his biometric data from all the way out here.
Once Babylon is able to extract all of the captain's information
They won't need him alive anymore.
:cue
Even just yesterday, I wasn't sure if you were gonna make it.
Remember what I said? Listen, your unni will never die.
Brother
I don't even have one photo with Brother.
Minhye
Is there anything after we die?
I don't know.
If there is, I hope we'll all meet again.
I don't.
I actually hope the opposite is true.
I'd like
Our paths not to cross.
I want them to live their own lives.
That was their choice.
That was what they wanted for themselves.
If you can respect that
Then you have to do your best to live on.
Even Jeong Jinman is just an independent contractor.
Nothing would ensure your business model's stability more than a partnership.
We're Asia's largest arms corporation.
Our reach allows you to access a larger market.
Rather than being stuck in Korea, a tiny market where firearms are illegal,
Are you open to thinking more globally?
A worldwide network with infinitely more diverse clientele.
How does that sound?
As you may already know,
Instead of dealing with a middleman like Jeong Jinman,
Dealing directly with us will streamline your process.
The options we provide enable you to widely expand your business model.
We brought you here today because you're influential among the Code Reds.
Please accept this as a small gesture of goodwill from Babylon.
Should we take care
Should we take care of that idiot lawyer?
He believes that Jeong Jinman was the one who attacked us.
I wouldn't worry about it.
That the reason the bus exploded that night
Was to cover up Bale killing Jun.
:cue
So tell me, how's the meeting going with our Code Reds?
Little Miss CEO, what are you trying to do?
The thing is
That isn't the only video we got.
Babylon General Lee Yonghan, you had him killed
As well as those yakuza at a nightclub who weren't involved in any of this.
And when Bale killed your Japanese mercenary,
You tried to frame it on Jeong Jinman, didn't you?
You really have been busy since you got here.
I was thinking about giving you one last chance. Or not.
Listen, miss, you're not exactly in the place to offer anything.
As your friends were dying and the shopping mall was burning,
You abandoned it all and ran with tears streaming down your face.
I think I must have overestimated you.
When we met, you showed nerve, some promise, something.
And now I think you don't have anything.
You'll immediately release Jeong Jinman or I'll release it.
Everything that Babylon's done to the world
I've got stored on this server.
If you did that, you'd kill him yourself.
- If he dies, then - Then what?
You die too.
K, there's no time. Right now, everything
KUSANAGI SUJIN $5,000,000 / CASH
That fucking cunt.
VACANT
OFF DUTY
They're all gathering at Jeong Jian's location.
So all the little vermin are teaming up to take my head, huh?
- Give me the coordinates. - Gangwon-do, Jeongseon.
North, 37, 24, 42 seconds. East, 128, 40, and 36 seconds, ma'am.
This is Kusanagi Jin. Head of Babylon, Korea.
I need to get a drone from Okinawa to Gangwon, South Korea, right now.
That is not something the Korean branch
Can act on independently without approval.
You're not listening.
If we're talking about approval, I rank higher than Okinawa.
We can say North Korea sent it.
This is what we do.
This is impossible to do unofficially.
Now listen here, whether it's official or unofficial
Isn't your concern, it's mine.
Send it.
Is this allowed?
It is now.
If it results in accomplishing the mission, everything's forgiven. :cue
Should we take care of that idiot lawyer?
He believes that Jeong Jinman was the one who attacked us.
- I wouldn't worry about it. -  I guess.
That lawyer's brain couldn't even comprehend what went on.
That the reason the bus exploded that night
Was to cover up Bale killing Jun.
Sir, shouldn't we let the staff know about this?
I'm heading out now.
I have your niece to capture.
MAKO 1. One minute until arrival.
It's a low-altitude mountainous region. We can't fly any lower.
That's enough. Take aim.
And fire.
Oh, shit. You couldn't crack it?
MAKO 1, you can pull back now.
Raise the security system to the maximum level,
Get everyone who is on standby, send them in, let Q handle point.
Where is Q? We need to leave now.
Patience, my friend.
She'll be here in a few minutes.
Raising security system to the maximum level.
The fire shutters have been activated. Yes. Yes.
Don't worry. A shot like that won't even make a dent.
You see, they'll have to actually come in and plant the flag, if they want this end.
I'm Jeong Jian, thanks for coming.
Let's get to business.
:cue
Q, kill every insect that's hiding inside. Make sure you crush them all.
And eliminate Jeong Jian. We don't need her now.
All teams. Send everyone in.
Team four, move out. :cue
Take cover!
The targets are approaching.
Open fire!
M. Wait.
Q.
Set it down.
That's not your knife.
Should we take care of that idiot lawyer?
He believes that Jeong Jinman was the one who attacked us.
I wouldn't worry about it.
I told you we have to capture him alive!
I was never the one that killed J.
In order to catch me,
Kusanagi lied and betrayed you, she used your anger.
That footage
How do I know that it's real?
The day your brother and Bale died :cue
A bus carrying Babylon staff exploded.
You must have heard.
That's every witness from that day, gone.
That the reason the bus exploded that night
Was to cover up Bale killing Jun.
You need to know how to make the enemy of your enemy your friend.
That woman killed Brother right in front of me!
I know this might be hard for you to accept right now
But just like how Pasin betrayed us
The line between ally and enemy is a sheet of paper, Jeong Jian.
What the hell is that?
I understand, I get it.
Then let me add one more thing.
Listen up, Uncle.
You're gonna get caught.
You're gonna let that woman take you.
Let's give Kusanagi exactly what she wants.
She'll need to extract our biometric data,
If she wants to take control of murthehelp.
She'll be a bit distracted when she captures my uncle.
In the meantime, we'll gather intel from the Code Purples and the mole.
I'm Jeong Jian, thanks for coming.
We need to pull in as many Code Reds as possible.
Once Kusanagi knows our location
They'll come to eliminate us.
It's a trap!
What happened? Report. What's going on, damn it?
If the operation succeeds,
Babylon's regular forces will be completely isolated.
Wait a minute.
Once Babylon extracts the data
They might kill Jinman.
Yep.
We'll have to trust her then.
The woman who brought him in.
I'm heading out now.
I have your niece to capture. :cue
Do you really think you can win?
This isn't a fight I'm trying to win.
I was trying to protect my niece.
After all, it's my fault that her life ended up the way it is now.
But we sacrificed too much for it.
I'm sorry about
Your brother.
The thing is
I always knew that someday this moment would come.
My younger brother and I were raised by yakuza.
I think I was around 10
When our clan boss took his revenge on our father.
He made us stay there and watch him do it.
He told us later that when he slit our father's throat, we didn't blink.
He said that we had this look in our eyes then.
That we didn't flinch or turn away.
That's when he decided to raise us as yakuzas.
That look in our eyes.
When I saw your niece, I saw the same look in hers.
You have it too.
And I know I still have it.
That's just the type of people we are.
If you keep a lion locked in a cage, her claws will get dull.
She'll forget her own nature.
I guess the choice is yours now.
Not true. It's Jian's to make.
Considering the bad choices I made,
I don't think it's a luxury I deserve.
Jian has already made her choice,
So what I'll do now is protect her with everything in me.
I think this is
As far as I can go.
Do you think we can meet again one day?
If we're still breathing.
Looks like that drink will have to wait again.
My name is
Ichika, okay?
Takimoto Ichika.
Report this to Q right away.
Shit, we're fucked.
Q, come in. Answer me now!
:cue
- What? I'm busy here. -  We have a serious problem.
The higher-ups know everything.
You need to come to the office immediately.
I was told "a certain person" is waiting for you on a video call.
Shit.
Has headquarters said anything?
Shit. No.
Oh, shit. Son of a bitch.
Don't move!
It's all right.
Hey, lower the guns. Yeah, it's all right. It's dangerous.
-  Yes? -  K,
Pull out of there immediately
- and return to headquarters. -  Sorry?
Do you mean right now?
We're in the middle of an operation.
From now on, that operation has nothing to do with Babylon.
Return to base. Immediately.
Huh?
It's not like I'm busy as hell or anything.
If it's urgent, he should come himself.
Where to?
Let's go home.
:cue
Hey, did you see the bus footage?
Yeah, what a crazy bitch.
I knew something was off from the start. Shit.
Are you fucking kidding me?
DISABLE SECURITY PROTOCOL?
Stay out here.
You sneaky motherfucker.
Hey, main gate. Stop that vehicle from entering!
Stop that goddamn bus!
That the reason the bus exploded
- that night was -  Can't you hear me?
- to cover up Bale killing Jun. -  Do you wanna die too?
:cue
Okay.
Seems like Operation Empty House is a success.
All we're doing is using her own playbook and turning it back on her.
How the hell did that bastard get out of that damn cell?
What should we do?
Let's just wait. Just a bit.
Lower your guns. Everyone, guns down.
Open the gate.
You all heard, I'm sure,
Most of Babylon's fighters have been buried under tons of rubble in our mine.
We expect that some number of forces will remain,
But our target is only
Kusanagi Jin.
If they aren't targets,
Please refrain from engaging with any unarmed personnel that are still inside.
Just priority one.
So these trashy little vermin really want to come after me, huh?
These fucking rat bastards. I have to do everything around here.
In the end, you're all you got. Fucking alone.
Shit.
:cue
Three o'clock.
You dressed correctly for the occasion.
Let's do this.
The real negotiation begins now.
Hey!
Come and get me, you ragtag motherfuckers!
Uncle
Are you okay?
Hey! Kusanagi's in front of the situation room!
Jian, get up!
Hold as long as you can.
Not a fucking chance.
We're connected.
So you are Jeong Jinman.
It's been 12 years since I've had to smell this disgusting gunpowder!
Are you trying to blackmail us with something Kusanagi did on her own?
That seems a little weak.
I'm just relaying to you what your employee did
During her time here leading Babylon Korea.
The blackmail would be the data we have on the server.
What is it that you want?
Peaceful coexistence between murthehelp and Babylon.
That's all I want.
"Peaceful coexistence."
Do you think such an idealistic relationship can last?
Peace isn't exactly good for our line of business.
I'm sure you know this since you were once a part of Babylon,
But we will not hesitate to break any lasting peace
For the sake of business.
Humans have been killing each other for thousands of years now,
And in the end your murthehelp is banking on that same human nature,
Making profit off human lives. :cue
For someone like that to be talking about peace
What a contradiction.
There have been times of peace, no matter how brief they were.
In that case
We can call it a ceasefire.
If Babylon were to accept my proposal,
I won't need murthehelp. Not anymore.
-  Uncle Cheolseung! - Don't worry, I'm okay.
Who the hell said you could negotiate by yourselves?
Put the gun down.
Your work here is finished now.
My methods were never a problem before. You'd just turn a blind eye, didn't you?
I did it all for the sake of Babylon. And now what? You're firing me?
All because of a lapse of judgment?
It was never "all for the sake of Babylon" to you.
You were only ever loyal to yourself.
Fuck that!
You pathetic little shits.
Mr. Jeong Jinman
You and I are both people who walk alongside the specter of death.
I swear, as long as I remain here
I'll honor our ceasefire.
We have a truce.
Then I'll take care of business over here.
But first
I'll make this clear.
Even if the most trivial piece of data leaks out,
For example, let's say, what a client had for dinner
Or the name of our client's dog.
If anything were to leak out,
Then you and your niece,
Along with anyone ever involved with your operation,
Will all disappear.
Make sure you honor your end.
We'll talk again, Jeong Jinman.
And you too
Jeong Jian.
Did everyone make it out?
Now what's the plan?
You're asking me that?
Then now
Listen up, Jeong Jinman.
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY KANG JI YOUNG